[{"answer": "I think he should get the exact amount of mercy he gave everyone in that theater.", "docId": "130401pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "And do you think that he should be executed if he's found guilty?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "The man is a coward.", "docId": "130401pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "Did you feel that in some way he was trying to cheat natural justice?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "I think that in a society that is as violent as ours, we need a lot of different ways to control it and the death penalty is one.", "docId": "130401pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "Has your view of the death penalty changed because of what happened in Aurora that day?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "I can only speak for myself and for my family.", "docId": "130401pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "Have you thought through what the additional torment of a trial, with all the details that may emerge about what happened, not just to your son but the others that lost their lives and were wounded would all come back?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "I have no interest in understanding him.", "docId": "130401pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "Are you any nearer having any kind of understanding why Holmes did what he did?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "I watched the senator today on CNN and it seems like everybody wants to point fingers at everybody else and talked about filibustering.", "docId": "130401pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "What is your view of the gun control debate in America right now?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "I say if you have to do your job by lying, you need to get another job.", "docId": "130401pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "What do you say to those politician who say, well, I'd love to -- I'd love to vote for an assault weapons ban but it may cost me my job?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "It was absolutely heartbreaking.", "docId": "130401pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "Let me ask you first, Dana, we had a pretty civilized discussion today on your radio show, but when you hear a man like Tom Teves speak so eloquently and just desperate for something to happen, what do you say to him?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "Well, first of all the murderer in Colorado who killed 12 people should be executed 12 times.", "docId": "130401pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "Do you really think in your heart that the correct response of a great nation like America to an appalling atrocity like Sandy Hook is to race to sell more guns, more ammunition, and to expand gun rights?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "I think if we are going to have the conversation about whether or not the death penalty is a legitimate form of punishment, that's a conversation that folks can have.", "docId": "130401pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "Now, when you hear those kind of statistics, I suppose the obvious question is this: Does a wrong conviction of somebody -- and we don't know whether someone being executed -- we have to presume, I would imagine that some may have been before this -- does that on its own not count enough for the desire to execute others?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "Look, there is a Second Amendment and it's important.", "docId": "130401pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "What do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "I think the sequester is responsible for the president not doing as well on basketball as he might.", "docId": "130401pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "So, finally, and very quickly, Grover Norquist, are you claiming responsibility for the president taking his eye off the ball?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "It's a great question.", "docId": "130401pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "And should they think about that going forward?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "You know, I think that this thing was just a fluke.", "docId": "130401pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "Would you jump in a different way if you knew there was a big drop off?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "Well, I think, number one, he has to do his rehab because, you know, when you're young, and you get hurt, Piers, you try to always rush and come back.", "docId": "130401pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "What is your advice to him going forward in terms of rehabilitation, not just physically, but mentally?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "Over I'd say less 10, 12 years, I've enjoyed such a degree of independence and freedom, I can basically do whatever I want.", "docId": "130401pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "Have you become homophobic?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "Yes, on the -- on the surface it sounds really bad.", "docId": "130401pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "Are you homophobic?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "To me it's an important difference but I don't think we have time to go into it right now, when you read it in the transcript, which I'd gone back and created, I can do a couple of things to show you and highlight --", "docId": "130401pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "What difference would that make?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "If the question is asked to make things simple for the audience and I believe that it is, I'd like to make it even simpler.", "docId": "130401pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "Are you somebody that objects to a gay lifestyle and to gay marriage?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "If you want to keep this simple for the audience, let me just give you a straight no, I'm not homophobic.", "docId": "130401pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "So you're not homophobic?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "Because the nature of spontaneous improvisation, I had done it a complete show as truth and then the audience requested reality.", "docId": "130401pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "Why didn't you know what you were talking about?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "Yes, I am very much so because what's being questioned is my support for that community.", "docId": "130401pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "Are you -- with all the members of the gay community who are outraged by what you said, are you -- are you sorry?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "130401pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "And do you have any problem with gay marriage?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "130401pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "Do you support it?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130401pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "So you support full gay rights?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "I mean that I have been diligently working for the last five years on a project that is if I have not managed to convince you that I have very much at stake in putting this question to rest is Michelle Shocked homophobic, does Michelle Shocked support the gay community --", "docId": "130401pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "What do you mean?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "Well, you've answered them very clearly and people can make their own minds up if you mean it.", "docId": "130401pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "Do you feel to your satisfaction?", "qSentId": 525}]